<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SOfIoTS | </title>
    <link>https://example.com/tag/sofiots/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://example.com/tag/sofiots/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>SOfIoTS</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://example.com/media/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>SOfIoTS</title>
      <link>https://example.com/tag/sofiots/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Socio-Technical Security Modelling: Analysis of State-of-the-Art, Application, and Maturity in Critical Industrial Infrastructure Environments/Domains</title>
      <link>https://example.com/publication/sofiot_report_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/publication/sofiot_report_1/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Industrial Internet of Things security modelling using ontological methods</title>
      <link>https://example.com/publication/iiotonto2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/publication/iiotonto2022/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secure ontologies for the Internet of Things: representing risk and security concepts using basic formal ontology</title>
      <link>https://example.com/publication/sofiot_report_4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/publication/sofiot_report_4/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SOfIoTS: Ontological Framework, Demonstration Outcomes, and Recommendations for Further Work (D3/D4)</title>
      <link>https://example.com/publication/sofiot_report_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/publication/sofiot_report_2/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secure ontologies for IoT Devices: a Review and Gap Analysis</title>
      <link>https://example.com/publication/sofiot_report_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/publication/sofiot_report_3/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secure Ontologies for IoT Systems (SOfIoTS)</title>
      <link>https://example.com/project/sofiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/project/sofiots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;style&gt;
div.a {
  text-align: center;
}

div.b {
  text-align: left;
}

div.c {
  text-align: right;
}

div.d {
  text-align: justify;
}
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;d&#34;&gt;
The SOfIoTS project aims to understand and develop cybersecurity attributes for existing Industrial Internet of Things (IIoT) network ontologies to include machine learning at the Edge. The project’s planned outcomes will result in publications on which further academic endeavor can be built, whilst contributing to the understanding and methodologies of data security and assurance in Building Management Systems (BMS) in sensitive public buildings.
&lt;br/&gt;The SOfIoTS project, in partnership with National Physical Laboratory (NPL), Cube Controls, RITICS, 4D-SIG and PETRAS SRF1 project, ELLIoTT, will undertake a comprehensive review of IoT Network Ontologies to identify gaps in security provision, particularly with respect to industrial, buildings and utilities control applications. This will draw upon experience and review data from RITICS and ELLIoTT.
&lt;br/&gt;
The project will look at the Semantic Sensor Network (SSN) Ontology (w3.org), to include local machine learning functionality, and to provide methods for mapping abstract representations to specific ‘in context’ configurations of application. The project will also create a dialogue to promote delivery and impact through RITICS and the 4D-SIG to the UK Digital Twins programme and to the Centre for Digital Built Britain.
&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Collaborations:&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://petras-iot.org/collaborate/&#34;&gt;Please refer project main website &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/br&gt;
&lt;b/&gt;Task and Responsibilities:&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;	Conducting substantive research within the SOfIoTS project into the issues/problems, ideas, concepts, or theories and applying appropriate methodologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;	Investigating the application of ontological methods to securely combining and fusing information from Internet of Things sensors with data frameworks associated with Building Information Modelling (BIM) and Geographical Information Systems (GIS).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;	Work with industry partners to explore the application of hybrid ontologies to the development adaptive and futureproof Digital Twins, with application in Building Information Modelling (BIM) and Product Data Modelling.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;	Investigate the emerging security threats, vulnerabilities, and potential impacts of cyber-attacks on industrial and building management systems (IBMS).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;	Liaise with industry partners to design, develop, and test (validate) an adaptive and secure ontological model for representing IoT-enabled socio-technical infrastructure system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;	Contribute to the drafting and submission of quality publications to appropriate and reputed peer-review national and international conferences and journals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;	Prepare and disseminate research outcomes through relevant academic and policy-themed workshops, and industrial forums.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;	To prepare project progress reports on research for funding bodies as required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;	To help develop suitable relevant web resources for disseminating/socialising project progress and results through social media.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;	Contributing ontological information systems insights into the wider research PETRAS programme.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;	To work within project’s financial budget constraints. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;	Contributing to the overall research activities with the research team at UCL including preparation and drafting of research bids and proposals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
