<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WoO-SAS | </title>
    <link>https://example.com/tag/woo-sas/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://example.com/tag/woo-sas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>WoO-SAS</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://example.com/media/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>WoO-SAS</title>
      <link>https://example.com/tag/woo-sas/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Objects based Smart Aging Services (WoO-SAS)</title>
      <link>https://example.com/project/woo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/project/woo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;style&gt;
div.a {
  text-align: center;
}

div.b {
  text-align: left;
}

div.c {
  text-align: right;
}

div.d {
  text-align: justify;
}
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;d&#34;&gt;
The aim of WoO-SAS (Web Objects based Smart Aging Services) project is to develop technologies and mechanisms to improve the life of a super-aging society. Some of the topics we are currently exploring include the development of self-Learning smart aging service objects, to design infrastructure for healthcare services to assist the elderly living, collecting and analyzing data from the wearable and non-wearable sensors in order to monitoring vital health conditions. The outcome of this project is the IoT data analytics and services platform which provides services to the elderly.
&lt;/br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Collaborations:&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;/br&gt;
In this project, our partners were the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.keti.re.kr/eng/&#34;&gt;Korea Electronics Technology Institute (KETI)&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.etri.re.kr/eng/main/main.etri&#34;&gt; Electronics and Telecommunications Research Institute &lt;/a&gt; and HUFS Information System Lab.
&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Tasks and Responsibilities:&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Development of Self-Learning Smart Ageing Service using Web Objects and Artificial Neural Network.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Design and developing of Infrastructure for healthcare services to assist elderly living.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Designing semantic ontology for the efficient management of user centering services.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Collecting and analyzing data from the wearable and non-wearable sensors in order to monitor health conditions and elderly behavior.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Analyzing and enforcing user privacy in the data collection and analytic.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
